You will be meditating for years,
please prepare for meditation
mp3
I'm trying the class will be equal with it was a
wonderful lesson with all the
volunteers I don't know if you saw
the poster outside there is only we
have about 200 volunteers here who
work very very hard
Mortiger gave I would like to
thank again and
[applause]
[music]
I had a subject yesterday forgot
last night impossible we talked about
impossibilities for example when you have a
quarrel with your husband in the kitchen this husband is
impossible or
cells and you know that the pen
comes from me because I
have seed in the world for the pen the dog does not have
such a son that is why he is a dog seed
makes you a dog or a person I have 7
arguments with all the pens who put there up
to 7 and pens yes only you can
visit you can't give all to another
person it is impossible are you ready to endure how to
put the seed there you need to give the pen to
another person and and and
when you see your pen opens
it sows the seed in your consciousness now I
yesterday we had three questions for the lesson
strip three hearts with my friends
right mantra will
give centuries  I asked three questions,
they know the answer, cut out, you don't know,
other people, three questions, the first, if
I have a pen in my hand, if a pen is in my hands,
if I have a pen, what happens that comes
from me because I gave a
pen to 30, you now have a difficult question, if
Marilla is in her hand, a pen that comes from a
pen, not what is it called, what is the
name of emptiness, computer Shen Kukshina,
Chinese, emptiness,
interesting, therefore, a person
who really understands emptiness,
they like to give it all to other people,
this is a sign that a person understands
emptiness,
they are polite and smile at everyone, they give everything to
everyone, they distribute things because they
understand emptiness, cool,
this morning we will do a meditation dance for
you, I talked to Aldo and they
told me where we haven't reached yet,
yes, where the meditations have reached, and we will go
even further, we will go through
eight steps,
go higher, the field in the elevator and reach the 9th
floor, and was meditating on our
teacher, they scolded this, in general, any
teacher and your life, your first, taught at
school, taught in life, mom and dad shade,
then you have a school teacher, a
teacher at work, then she, you have
Teacher, wife, later, you have teachers,
children, maybe you have a spiritual
teacher, but in this meditation with
passion, we will ask three questions. The first is to
think if there is some teacher in
your mind. The
second is from
and Newman, to be the end and evaluate if there is a
teacher in your mind that comes from
your seeds. To 3, if it is impossible to calculate from your
mind that does not come from your seeds,
what message from the teacher is the
sound and the finished lid until
now, the project to wake up is all not with me and
so there is no teacher in
my mind that does not come from me and
this emptiness now I said that if you are a
good person, if you understand
emptiness, then you will give things to other
people. 2 types. If you do not understand, I will
put it, but you will not give things to
other people. If you understand just like
that, you will respect the teacher that
comes from you. And if you do not understand
emptiness,
you do not respect the teacher and carry the family
teacher teaches and taught, then they leave.
Therefore, in meditation, all your teachers,
parents,
school teachers, the person who taught
you your work, and we must respect them,
and this sows a new 7, then study will be with
us, stay
cool, it will be so, let's  First,
clear your throat, we are meditating in a group,
so please be attentive,
try to be quiet, create
sounds, we would like to meditate a little longer with
this, so sit
comfortably
in a normal meditation, we begin by
observing with breathing. Here we will begin
by observing the sound of air
conditioners.
Place your mind on the sound of the air conditioner,
the pipe of trouble. Don't forget the special
breathing technique in meditation. When you
exhale and reach the end of the exhalation, then
exhale a little more air. When you will
never be nervous during
meditation, and so we listen to the air conditioner,
this is the Scandinavians
and absolutely please move on to the heart.
After the period, observe the heartbeat. Get
drunk.
We are not yet inside the heart. We are simply
observing the heartbeat.
Now, dive inside the heart and the
heart beats around us and inside the heart is
not some dark, damp place. It is a very
beautiful room with a lot of sunlight. After all, they will
come to me alone.
Remember to do the breathing technique, an
additional exhalation,
ergotelis center.
Now we will dive into the very center of
the heart and the heartbeat will sound
far from us.
Now let's  Let's put a small
sugar crystal in ours.
From the outside, the crystal looks very
small, but when we put our mind inside,
there is a very comfortable room for
meditation
with lots of sunlight.
Come on, my layers of dough, Pacifica,
now I make mine as big as the
Pacific Ocean with people who have it,
spreading throughout this whole world,
quiet, deep, for
us, these two holes, exe,
remember to do with an additional exhalation,
Magadan,
now add to this the blue sky
expands from the bottom of the ocean to the edges, the sky,
I am in the landing, a scientist, double,
now we decide to turn off ours, how to
turn off the light bulb in the room, if a
thought arises,
block it and
give Alex, Alex,
remember the additional exhalation,
places
home, them to maintain sex,
now if I have thoughts and
images, just let them pass by,
don't fight, the sum
says the pastor,
now we are ready to begin meditation,
please choose one of your
teachers in life, maybe it's mom or
dad, a school teacher, or a
dharma teacher, and ask them to joyfully come to
you and meditate with you, and the teacher
comes and is very happy, the teacher is not a
picture, it's a real person with breathing
and learned, looks at you with great
love
and learn  It's cute, it's afraid because you're
meditating and the teacher knows that it will
help you, so let the teacher sit
opposite you with the
index taemin from the meeting to the jeweler.
Now think about some quality of
your teacher that you really
like, for example, patience or hard
work for other people,
and the teacher is like a pen, and so all the
good things that I see in them
come from me. I must have planted the
seed for this in my past life. The
first law of karma is the creator of the
seed, which is similar to the result.
If my teacher is very patient,
I must have been very patient in my
past life. If my teacher
helps many other people, that being
helped a lot of other people in my past life.
Let's dive into a journey through a
past life and just imagine where I
lived, like a hundred years ago,
what my job was, what I looked like, a
man or a woman, what kind of
family I had, and what I did to
see these wonderful qualities in my
teacher. So you have freedom in this
meditation. Create a beautiful story. Don't
hesitate to create a movie, and you will be the
main character in this movie, and we will walk
here for a few minutes, so
enjoy. Sometimes you will get
distracted, you will think about lunch.  100
slowly come back will see
how meditation and so
discography now please
return to the teacher and once again
enjoy this wonderful quality of
your teacher and to you and you can
ask 3 questions again first then can a
video with injections if taught my teacher
this wonderful quality I am
Martin and
second place from feathers ways of the company
this wonderful quality happens I
will change my
mother
third that is and spin-off about a century of
information does this wonderful
quality come from your own country and the
answer is no yes this emptiness
and pay a grin of strength
if mom is a teacher and there is emptiness then I
can keep my teacher in my
life always
when I return home from Thailand
if I share with other people
who are interested in these teachings carefully carefully
here I will sow the
seeds to see that my teacher
stays with me
Dutch somehow
now we respectfully ask our
teacher to leave meditation and we
descend to the eighth level 8th floor in
my mind thoughts in images arise I ignore them
I am very very quiet calm my mind
can speak but I do not react to this
remember to do an additional exhalation
now I  I'm moving to the seventh level, this is
my distance.
If thoughts arise, I measure them, block them, and
keep them calm.
Now, I return my mind to
the ocean and the sky.
Now, move only to the
very deep ocean.
We should talk about the interest of Yugorsk.
Now, move softly to the
sugar crystal, it's very small, and
remember, an additional exhalation.
However, 10.
Now, come back. The center of the heart. The heart
beats in the distance.
Now, we dive inside.
The heart and the walls beat closer to you.
And when you read, it swells,
and now return to your body and
observe the heartbeat in your body.
Your 3. And now, at the end of the meditation, 3
long exhalations.
Elena Panina.
Open your eyes and stretch with the
elements of the principles. This is a new, unified
new principle called "don't lingi bomb."
Say "don't lingi bomb."
Your language is like my capes, they taught me
Chinese. I told my Chinese
friends and they watched and "don't try,
and she will become, and we will put them on." And wallpaper,
when we were born, main,
we received bodies, and you are boarding at the
airport, and
You go to rent a car, how do you pay and
get a car, new boy, the same
story when you were born, the
moment you get a rental car,
line carry, you buy a car,
why don't I say that you buy a
car and because you need to return, yes, that's right, it was
0 dollars, you need a cop,
it's temporarily rented, a guide from a couple, we
get this body here in Lipetsk,
double, and this body is cold right
now, sometimes it's too hot, get this body, it
can get hungry,
I have a friend, he said, I
will never eat animals, and then she got very, very
hungry, and all her friends ate
fish, and she also ate fish, she decided
to be a vegetarian, but she got very
hungry, and there is no more food, Sochi file
and height of things,
so in the end she ate fish, a minivan
disk, so when you rent this
car,
you will do bad things in order to
take care of this, remain on the
fact that this car, she's not a very good
wife, she requires 32, 3 times a day,
need a sweater,
many needs, of course, everyone in this
room is a good person and shot
integer, no one here will steal anything,
like very few places on earth where  500
people on YouTube, you can
leave your wallet here, no one will
take it. Everyone is Buddhist, but you, damn, by
names, if they really need it,
their mother is sick, for example, or the children
need help, they will take it. Everyone,
including me, will choose. We grow up, we are the same, and that's why
we have this. We try
to be good people and not harm
others,
but if we don't have food, we will steal. This is
human nature. I
grew my own herbal bar.
We will steal in order to feed the body.
Disco Love Live on the Collector
and
in the next life we ​​will get
rental cars again Tyrlin will only weaken
the disk
but this car will be again the same
type
not Tesla this is an old American car
constantly breaks down and days this very needed
light-loving is needed this is not very
good yet inside inside clouds blood meat
bones at a price of more than 5000 important things in
your body
and they cooperate
lungs are fighting heart but he could
lungs want more cooling heart
needs more heat
they fight with each other this is live in if the
lungs win in players we will freeze
if the heart wins in warm it will be
hard for us to breathe dreamer to see
she five thousand parts fighting with each
other
monster well yes I translated for the great from a
traditional doctor for several
and he said an interesting thing - when
lungs and heart it is very abnormal
unusual therefore a healthy person is
not the norm a
sick person is the norm therefore
health is temporary therefore to get
food even for good people and dreams tenant
if in this hotel I will have food and if in
this hotel there is no food we will steal poison
in order to survive in the war everyone
will  do bad things to us yes and but
when we die spinning rods because of
stealing food we will get this type of
body next time from one point of
view it is very cool to have this business we
rent a car
but it is not very good quality why will it
turn out we did bad things to
get this body
and now listen we got to this part
we have
things to do this this is such we
must eat we must work for a long time
your rear and if we do not have food we will steal
if we steal what is it called.
Next time we will have this type of
body, body, body, a link is born, and
this is
samsara, this is proof of samsara,
so we need to get out of it, we need to
change it. If you saw the emptiness
directly, the
Yangtze, then the body will begin to change from the inside,
and later you will not have such a body, you
will have it, it will not need it, and it will not
harm other people, to get
food, it will live forever, a warrior
.  First, it's very cool if you have it,
you can help people in different
cities at the same time, it's effective, the body
doesn't age, the oars are a real Tesla
Model X, a
rented car, that's why we have
such an example, we
need to change it,
we need it, take it, don't wait until it's time to
return to the airport, while
in the hammer
you will see emptiness, okay, Baku resident,
and other things in your life don't work,
because magicians are not an ambulance for many,
so changing the matter is urgent and the
best method is a horse, my horse, that's
why we spend so much time, peace,
beep-epip, I know you need to go to the toilet, take a
break, as my teacher would say,
I'm still not with my beloved,
let's go for a little while and I will
[music]
we
will stay with her for a little while, Lenin, kancha, you'll
go, hybner,
peak, here, a couple of eight bytes
because this body was made bad,
flax seeds, we will always have problems and she will
always be sick, she will always ask for the
toilet, or even if you don't have an illness
right now, or maybe there is just
mania, maybe we already have cancer,
it's just not  A friend of ours showed up to go,
she got it
now, and we were very surprised. Oh, you
were in class, maybe for another month. You looked
good. I didn't know I had cancer. It's
growing inside. Igor, war. So this
body, even if you feel good
right now, don't worry.
You'll feel bad. From the previous
videos, this is the nature of our body. Everything is crap.
We need to change it. Innocent, we slept at the
camp program. This body has
bad karma, its opposite, and to keep us
alive, we need to do bad karma.
But this is crap, and then we, the king of
sociality, point out that samsara has two
reasons. Oklo, your pride, and now
our class will come to these two
reasons. We'll talk about them literally. The
first is bad seed, bad
seed, which makes
the pen, and this is what they are similar to, and both
come from here. The
body is our business. A
shaved door is my bad karma. This is the first.
In the past, perhaps I ate meat, and because of us,
they killed the stomach.
[music]
10,000 chickens are killed in China every year,
10 billion tiempo legend.  I took an apple
and they also have a body, but they also don't want to
survive.
We're not years old. When is the day when you go to the
ring to eat French fries, eat salad, and
people's, please don't believe it.
Human hands are now under scientists
have discovered that meat contains, as we
call it, polystyrene. The main
source of polystyrene is meat.
65 percent of the American population
eats meat and they get cholesterol.
Four hundred thousand die annually from KFC.
And it seems, yes, please don't eat Gamma.
You can make a green drink. This
makes Fore Esik. All my friends, I
think, became a vegetarian. 40 years ago,
defend me. You're on the way. And my friends
were told you won't have a printer. Stay.
You'll get sick,
and it takes you, and you won't be healthy. You
don't need a warehouse. This only creates
problems for people. We're flying through the forest.
Guy, and so two things are the reason for
this body: 1. Food chaos, except that there
are reasons for food for the edict on
such things. Denis, give it to
Sam and Gilly, and well, these dishes. Killgrave
and Moss are very famous at home. Comfort
Shutter, both.  Darma porridge chapter 4 take out the
mountains let's do the whole secret
Lelya detail jack the nation above the statuses
Indian all the stars you see in
the sky
come from karma
named Simba Waris to someone not [ __ ] what
is karma karma is forties and coma is
the most basic pocket and these are thoughts you are not
tempo and such when you think it's karma
now we create a lot of different
karmas all for this battle comes in and we
takin' that's why we have
3com each of the brain go to the hatches and
thinking this is the most basic feed 3 houses
Kelly and secondary kama and secondary
feed what you say and what you do
dose USA
here goat they provoke this
body of
feed of what you say and do this
what we say and think provoked by
our thought Dogan he
therefore thought occurs a second before
speaking he in any bifa I'll go out center and a
second before we do something
we think something too cold I
should say an hour we don't sit we and
when we see jazz  You think, ma, yes, who are you
making karma for? The body of this ball is
karma. I think it's worth it for us. You and they will
say something about the
report. What did you like about the class?
Everyone is happy. Contribution with KMU.
People. This class is
very good for Eskimos. A fragment of dive
in dealing. If the Eskimos come,
they will like the class. Since then, and thinking,
but a second before that, I won't stop
talking. And something did
the Eskimos have such holes in their houses. Kama Tenge, that
is, maternal karma is thinking and
conclusions. The wall is midori.
So, if we're going to understand who
did this, how we did this,
see Andy's body, stands, nannies, and we need to
understand the karma of thinking
before mixing. So, we'll spend two or three
tracks. Secretary, there's a ping to study the
karma of thinking. Ok, and we'll give them ponds and how we
can improve it. It's better, and then it will
change the body.
Now we'll take a 15-minute break.
Break.
300 GHz Oxysize. And he goes and does
some exercises to warm up. See you
in 15 minutes.
And the hares are beating off. And as I said earlier, I'm already
teaching from La Marine.  8 years if you can, it's
good if you hear something from the
previous 8 years, review with pictures,
so I'll do a review with pictures, but
young, I usually do this in the evening, but this
evening we have another time,
especially fire, good, we
also have three weddings, what is the value,
I have two meanings, yes, there was the first one, they knocked out
about whom we burn our old headlights,
the payment came in,
so during the
fire, we our old one, we throw
fire and it burns and Fion,
if you want, you can live broadcast for businessmen,
debates, me, if you did some
big bad deeds, lived and all of
us made beauty, and I also do Marat
Gelman, monkeys, his new one, if I
tell what I did when I was young,
so write it down on a piece of paper and at the end of the
day, we ask for three days
[music]
and some especially experienced teachers,
some of them did a three-year
silent retreat, we have
several teachers here who did a
three-year silent retreat,
Wallace, than Jun, 1, this chin, dream, out of 10,
1 remained, this is the way of
will and very Michael, 1 is where Sean is  Michaels
[applause]
Owl and on the DVD
they will help us with the fire his Konstantinov
and you also something else in the carriage
we will give you a plate
you take it and put it in the fire for a long time
like this
do it like this for Oleg's hands so
elegantly that's how it should be
[music]
be it with style like a girl beautiful
think about it I threw out mine cried
written this first decomposition concession
victories as if they love when you repent
never be afraid to tell your
teacher you will become the
worst thing you did they
happily to honestly you can't lie on the
target so you can clean this seed
if you talk about it so drink
his pain and well and derbets
I did a bad thing when I was young
new years ago and also and as if they love the
smell is true this is the thing you want
now I will give run away and new day it's
good to tell the teacher about the good
things you did 35 units it's also
good to tell very warm and the candle
which you made
and this smell is very pleasant for them
conclusions and we will  It takes
time to improve. Become a good person. We are bad
people.
It won't change in one or two years, but I was able to make
small, gradual progress. Poverty has made
many big mistakes. I would give it back even now.
So please don't fall down and
don't say I'm a bad person. What is this
really? We're soldering a cube, but you're improving little by little.
It's good to give resin. This
DNA is for a bird, a storm,
it will find inspections or damage in places,
and this smoke will gradually reach the whole
world and it will bring peace to other people. 500
people in Thailand light their
bad seeds. This smoke will touch the
whole world. It will spread everywhere. It will
give people sensations. Therefore, there are two
goals. One of the two is
peace. If you're tired, you don't have to
stay. It takes two and a
half to three hours.
If you feel happy, go and be happy. You don't have to
stay until the last
minute.
We will have some laws and snacks.
So have fun. Life is difficult. If
you need to enjoy the time of year, they love
you to be happy. The goal of Buddhism
is to be happy. The slide was published
if the staff is on,
so while you're walking, Buddhism, you need to
rejoice. It got in the way. I stopped for an hour.  I
was happy,
so now I want to go home to sleep
and watch TV. To be a bride, if there will be, don't
be such a Buddhist
[music]
review of Star on Demand, and that's why
we don't have more
time today, it's not that, it's not that,
show, and so now I'm going to
review the part where it talks about
how to study, and click on the picture of
the person who drinks coffee,
this part of this program will be,
so go to class, listen to the
class, and after class, go to the female to have a
drink and some coffee, it's
very tasty, there is this 1 tenge, in class,
I drink a green drink,
AvtoKraz, and this is a PS3,
after class, joy, cookie, one link,
and talk about what you heard in
class
three times, this is a tradition, videos with your
friends, and the system exists, but
surely it checks James's stash
from that day, and other indexes, what
you heard is expensive, this is Barry, I sewed, I
talked about the body, it will go to the
moment, then he talked about a
rental car,
which I don't remember, two of a fence, take 3,
4 friends,
why did you come in, someone will say, I fell asleep, I
loved this part.  A friend and then he
suddenly tells about what he was talking
about rental cars among India 9
he will say well, did you like the
presentation Jimmy and I fell asleep during this
part and let's repeat this get infected
this is an old tradition 2000 years figurine
go drink tea coffee take cookies
don't tell anyone about the cup
eat them and talk about GD 7
this is the most fun first is very-very
important Wembley
in order to remember all the spirits
this tradition ball fig next drawing
Mr. Nick I am called how to think about
yourself and about sex is called think that
you are a sick person sickness
think that you have a disease
spiritual cancer you are visiting and think about
these teachings mediven for any as a
cure for you video from give away
countries doctor went through all the teachers like
Dr. Dan up to 30 years miracle star
and all the teachers together for as medical
staff
entity
study and know-it-all to me it's like a cure
for oversized maybe our body is not
sick are you
but our heart is sick constantly so
when you come I took each one
friends ask you  Do you take
medications here with and there 2-3 times
a day to fix
my mind and heart
a thousand defy in this tradition think about
what I need to come invoice
received as a doctor there is a doctor of course there is an
inspection there is a
small doctor there will be a hospital director
I work well as my wife
people ask why Jasmine gave
people these robes doctor's
robe you see
escape to teachers you are here for apple this is an
opera been in da common people and will
tell you the story of a famous person
[laughter]
him disgusting-the monkey king of hell
finest and according to this story of famous people
you machines think computer biker
some teachers to go to
go that's why they
invited him you don't believe to see where the
park you will be why is this where he will be for the
first time taught I don't want I don't want to go to the
park there are no deer and the
arguments of the city you don't want an opera no but I do
n't want to hear about Schwartz on I want to be
chanson
Olga Dibtseva I don't want to go to a generation
and see where I will be for the first time taught
Stalin
I will be here I want to study Lam-Rim to
become  Brenda, his son, about me,
and then they will sing about me,
so this is the tradition of Lam Rim, and about 5 thousand
years ago,
Nick taught vocals at Garshin here,
and by the way, I will not walk around
any of these five, respect, and an old film
with sense, many reptiles, it is good to study
the stories of
saints, as the Times itself blows on Garshin,
do this, but spend most of your time on
his truth in your practice,
a cube, and you will become tired and
give them perhaps to make yours, would
you now become a show and study auto taught,
let's tell you to work,
sometimes illuminated, want to make your home a
sacred place,
people will come, 5,000 years she was an ordinary
person, then she began to study dance,
then she saw, just give you a look, I'm
studying, on this day, her body
began to change, and she became, they will be in
this house, people can walk around
you, don't constantly think in thoughts
about old Buzov, you are the next model, and they will
walk around your house, bad
for blessings, this is true, so
prepare it for, perhaps you can
charge money for walking around
your house, 118 sap, three hours after
attention,
this picture should  remind you of the master of
media find
when you are sitting with your friends in a
cafe
stage you can play in the picture even before
5 show the picture give 7 this is
sung what is the meaning of Harrison Bobby Campo
here they will write a song you to me after
I became guys much more expensive
injection have not heard about I think that
evening pictures
it is not the fault the theme is the fault too busy
you please for dinner now can you while
fears can you please picture
we talk with you don't forget this is
yours they are putting a lot of pressure on Magomedovna
now there are problems no but Gandhi Sagar
don't Finns you know
100 years ago there was no penicillin Bukina
duo Parthenon people
we couldn't do operations on people they
died
info-chan from infection and on the wound
data disk in olefins and then they discovered
penicillin and Wi-Fi is dangerous if you
do an operation then you
inject penicillin and Volga
Anakin and you will not get an infection and will not
die
if there is no penicillin perhaps you will die
and now there are problems itself some
people have become insensitive to  Penicillin,
these bacteria have learned to fight
penicillin, so for some people,
penicillin no longer works. Bar and dates,
these bacteria in the body have
adapted, and when you give them
penicillin now it no longer works.
Why are we talking about this? Disc C of this
class is to overcome negative
thoughts
and we will study a large list of
negative 84,000. Very depressed, there is
desire, but different anger, great. There is a
purpose for coming here to study according to stats.
Blue Domain Gun is simply the main
weapon to defeat these 84,000.
If your husband is on you, you remember the pen and
you talk about me,
any new film, Death movie, and you change
your seed here I bark, don't yell at your
children, don't do it on xenon.
I'm 40 years old already.
Some students are with me, 25 years old,
diesel recently,
and someone came, the godfather was hanged. I have a
problem with my husband. Do
you have a suggestion and don't say anything? I
've heard for many years. Don't say anything. I need
something new.
DG, em, es, ist, im, there foam.  Finns,
they've developed an insensitivity to
idols. I've known China for a long time. You
want me to help you, but you don't want
to hear. What do you love? Can you make something out of you?
Hang it up. Tell me something new.
I couldn't think of anything. Sorry, I
gave you an atomic weapon. Use it. Do you
want a slingshot?
I don't sell slingshots. I only sell them. I
can't make you small. Like a husband who
makes a husband. Can you find a book at the airport on
how to fix it? A man who makes a
Honda.
Talk to him. I'll dream of it at night. Ask him not to
shout. You have a family.
I don't sell this. They sell penicillin. You do
n't need to get used to it. If you
come here three or four times and you don't
use it, then when you return home,
you'll stop listening to it. One held. You
won't hear about it. 3-4. You won't hear
what I'm saying. And a million strings of my
truly old, different years. When I
lift the handle, they crawled and instantly fell
asleep. Our home. So, if
you have trouble falling asleep,
ask me at home. Find me in Ukraine.  Ask your
friend to invest well the first time
you heard it, didn't give it and he'll
hear three times nothing
big will
not hear q load right now with
his mouth and details no need just
come Thailand is constantly going here no
need to talk about hanging you already taught the
pen last time barking fits perfectly
why are we teaching the pen again
because you are constantly with your husband and
and if you stop arguing with your
husband I will stop Chen Iru do I agree
next
next picture visit yes take him not here
I am this John Brady when he was young I
want no one a hundred years ago and Fiat is
if you look so closely or you
again a little hair what is he doing
probably pushed Intuit at the computer
sedans new single
this is 2007 at a conference he collects
money we need to save old books
you 2 gems on the eighth we talk about this
cars and became at home after you
study you have a responsibility
and Pirlo
help keep her alive in the world when
you can see a map with all
religions by measures
practically died these races already  They
practically disappeared.
I was at the airport in Shenzhen, but without a
whole
osmo, findings, manting, daspin,
they sell in the morning, a diamond cutter, and a
small one on his, this steel, syufa. I wanted to
study the seam at Canada, FIFA, masters seam, and
thank you for wanting to study first of all,
muffins, you can study
fittings,
we've been studying 15 generations,
and he didn't tell the first few,
what's the point at all? I don't know, you're 15
generations already, you write these words, ns and house
seam, but you don't know the meaning of this.
Keep the books alive and keep the
meaning alive. There's no kiba. We need to
save books. API skates. The book one.
Xiaopi should save some. We ourselves,
but you need the meaning. Save the
video.
This is your job. You need to help. After
all, how to pay for the cap as if
kindness Buddha. Make sure they don't
disappear anywhere. Each generation has a hole on it.
You were your angel. Di Da Mix 3.
We need to save the books and pass them on to the
next generation. From under the water, this is
your
army. Wynn's stones. After you
got here, she's life at home. After
you heard, yes, if you  Heard about
two husbands in the kitchen after you have,
respectively, and before the bay,
pass on books to the next generation. Next
explains the next generation found
Stan, another MTD.
My job is coming soon, and your
job is starting to weave.
You are the next generation. The ruler is worth it.
Your work will begin in Begin with five. This is
your job, and each generation must
pass it on to the next generation.
Or is it all dead? Didn't become the next
disks? Yes, this child caught a cold, got
sick, and the joints are he taking medication. It's
important for Anatole's child to take medication, and he is
also present. Brazenly, Selam Rome, 400
dollars. No, not even 400 dollars. He
gave
4, and for 100 dollars, Shaman King,
you're screwed.
If anyone guesses, the state is strong. Drink it, and the
hadiths. She will repeat the question. Tell me,
we want to use a medicine that
is emptiness.
This is true, but it's not the same. Aspirin for that
menu doesn't matter. I was looking for it.
Look. He takes it while
listening to the genome. They took it away. He takes it
when he listens to the name of
the picture. Okay, I'll tell you the meaning of
the index.  During class,
use medications. Yandex. During
class,
use medications. Don't wait until you
get home. You can start index. You
can start running. Legrand right
during class. You're sitting next to someone. A
shoe or you're cold. I hung it up
for the casting. Custom: Excellent. I was walking. They're
teaching the handles. New, not comfortable. By the way, we
turned off the air conditioning, but this morning I was
also cold. And while I was teaching the emptiness, the
handles were coming out of you. I was thinking, why
then did it become cold? What's wrong with
this darkness? What's arbitrary?
I'm not taking medications immediately. During class, you
understand. You understand. There's a very deep
meaning. In the world of cards, you don't need to walk around for two days with
medication. I hung it up, then you need the
medicine.
Goodbye, you don't need it yet. In your pocket, Alan, knot
and legs. I use it when I get home.
Use it during the eyes. Why did you take
the end? Didn't turn it on? Oh, it's coming out of me. You
understand, there will be a sea.
Who made a move in the room? You made it.
Take your medicine. Cool. Ice.
I saw how the team concert air conditioning. Who
made the topic. You understand. Did the
air conditioning teach Team too much today?
But who made Team? We'll see when you talk
about it in class this morning. Peaceful.   That's
why  use it every
instant even during sleep left to
study in the fire we will burn our
bad seeds store
right now probably the path to begin
analysis.
Don't think I'll start, how long ago
Malvina,
when will I have lunch, do my own, eat, do it
on time, class, thousand, Miss Katie Merhenmil,
or take your medicine immediately, Helen,
this is a tradition, on time, because you're
too busy, you'll be packing your things for the
airport, you'll be prescribed, start
practicing now, the end, and Dumas' throat, and
practice, the mommy, do
n't tell me, it's cheap, I'll do the practice
tomorrow morning, you practice, he'll give it, but no,
do the practice on this chair, now
I have to wait, it'll be irrigated in 5 minutes,
this is Kerry, this is not who sings
rock and roll tomorrow, what I think he'll do
is about motivation
to be a teacher, and that's why we have them in this
room, they worked very hard.
They would have rushed, you began to throw on 20
years, but they started as you did not arrive,
knew, we were cooking 30 years ago in my, his
teacher, and they listened, practiced, N&D,
become Peter, and they became teachers on the
UAH council, this is a big part of having a game,
you guys can do pickup.
It's very important guys that you became
teachers, this is a very important view and you
must do this and it's my dream for
you to become teachers,
I will be ready after, in
general, this is about when you become
three things that you should
beware of literalism, not the first is
money, people of a people will give
you money, you are ready, this is very good to do, the
teacher's attitude pray, have money,
money is useful, we need, we need
money, what to pay for planes and all that, this is a
bridge, impul, but this is not the most
important thing, [ __ ], and Wynn's
Fomin, what the teacher wants from you from his practice, this is your practice, war right now you feel cold towards you and fingers if I see that you are like this, yeah, yeah, you, you look there where that day in your head if you do this for the Hopi birds and then the teacher now
we call it an offering to your
practice
if tests are the best offering if
you give money there after class I
thank you, but this is you come to me in the
act if you come next year,
points to Bali actions and you say
Herzen and since I arrived in
cash  Rome,
my husband and I are much younger, and I don't
expect every day to be perfect.
This won't happen. 10 million years of
arguing
and covering the enzyme, no, you won't change. One
year, the house didn't expect GPS. You'll have
depression. Tons of spectrum.
Don't expect this. Michael became Deadpool.
Kesha Michael has been studying this all his life. Jeremih.
This place and every day he makes
mistakes. Let's be honest, but for us,
his charm is next year. And
tell us about our marriage. We generally quarrel every day.
One by one. A way to fight. Now, one
day a week, we don't quarrel. Yes, this is the
best offering. Study. We don't become a
titel when you become a teacher. House,
don't think too much about 1 ha in da
Himba kettle. We can do everything while I wouldn't.
We don't need more. A big gap.
I taught 2 tone xp from my car for many years.
I'm an actor in his place. Don't
expect everyone to respect you in
class. They'll talk about hanging up. I
love you.
This will lead to big problems. Students are
like children. William. We love studying, but it
doesn't bring much, so students will
bring you problems. Videos of mothers over the king of
recreation centers. State companies can blame a
bad employee in this. Mom's, but a
mother can't blame children and Fireball. And
you're free. Sometimes you can't
do that. It's a lifelong blue. Guys,
these seniors, I don't know what students are like and
that some children don't even grow up to 70,
but you can't fire them. Transfer. And
students,
after you started teaching, what day,
that is, rest, in this tradition, you can't. Do they
respect you?
Like
Danny DeVito. God, yes, and they. He brings
problems every day. Achieve your goal. This is the
job of a teacher. House spectrum. 7th grade.
Life made of cotton wool. Monster. Don't think, don't
expect that life has decided. This is life.
Everyone loves. This is not so. Mom,
adenoids, century work.  Mom, it's very difficult
for you, never always, it's just like don't
think that you'll become very
famous. Don't expect this. A lot of
work. Mom knows this is the most pleasant work. The most
important thing is work, and work
worked better. People asked. It's cheap, I
think, teaching. Here's your advice. The first is the
hardest job in the world, but
second, and before my hair, I've been doing this
my whole life. Life, yes, the happiest
life, which not only can be, there's nothing
happy about. It was the first bridge, you're the
faculty, the hardest job,
well, the most problematic. Children are a
problem, but students are an even bigger
problem. Bad is not being done,
but there's no better job in the department. Can I
do this all my life? I'm incredibly
happy. I still have problems
collecting money, money, being fried by
buffs,
and Ken Atley gets to me. I can't sleep at night. We have him
day and night. Franchette, now I will
achieve this.
This is the best job in the world, the best
work,
therefore, the speaker, but motivation must be
pure.
[applause]
[music]
motivation don't expect that you will become
don't expect that people will give him don't
expect respect or presented
vagabov
90 percent of you from students and be
happy and care this is that adobe
reader there is no better job and damon title and
dima 122 reviews this is
this site with warehouses this is a
big white college this is 1 fear
further that's why I want a hand and lemoine title we
eat 122 brushes richard still happy
show a picture don't show words and
repair we eat 122
[music]
okay I already they tell you there are
122 and up to 100 dollars
I already told you people make
chasing
different packaging it's crap
no I'm cool but you're close
this is a woman
[music]
be an angel for everyone
this is about this is not exactly this is about that no not
exactly I told you what we already
talked about
[music]
teach other people cancer hands will be
beautiful because  It's as if they'll come to look at you,
even if you're teaching
your family in the kitchen, the sound of all the Buddhas will
come and they'll check it out. It'll be pretty good. The hands will come
when you teach. A Buddha will
come,
you'll smell, they'll taste like a human being. And as you
understand,
please, when you get home,
teach your hands well, your family, your
family,
especially if your friends are fighting with your husband.
Teach even two husbands of cars. Of course,
they will improve, but even more importantly, they will
come and like it because they love when
someone teaches hands. Here are my old
students.
We'll be found. When I teach hands, they
fall asleep, but while they're sleeping, everyone will
come and listen. So, I got out some
bikes. I need a couple of
beautiful microphones. I have water and gas for you.
I'll be considered, otherwise, it turns out, Adana
gave
[applause]. So,
what donor? I'm a hundred dollars to mine, in my opinion,
what will you and your husband announce?
Sets of money tonight. We
can give ourselves for this money. Invite us to dinner
and for $100 of hers,
he agrees, and places, people, and
you, he will solve the issue.
[music]
Romance salon  And 7 tasks of Szeged,
autumn, on Grandpa, I have a replacement, chi chi bi,
my wallet with
my question. You teach us to see
each person, we
will, but in the sutras, we are also told to stay
away from people with bad behavior.
If we are new students, what should we do?
Good frames, two types of friends, off,
tick-tock, tick-tock,
that's how they are, they will come to your house. You
can go, let's repeat, lam rim,
let's drink coffee, Latvian
pies, duels and parades, a miracle, we
call them man, there, dorman, friends. Yes,
you have here, without wasting your time, there is a top hat,
they are also sitting in the room, forget about it.
Come on,
Spider-Man, he came out of the bones, let's see,
gives Avanti, an action
movie, a wig. I went watching, and our
group, Shanghai, I think he finished
this block at this point and learned. You
have a choice. 12 other socks,
Danish, one asks, let's repeat,
lam rim, and the other, the second moment, the second smoke, he is
like a demon, to learn, the second friend, you
should say thank you. I love movies,
maybe we can go tomorrow.
Keshava said that sometimes we need at least
from Laos, a toilet.  and I also decided you want to
look at the bunks
from people omsa empty
review but today I have to become
Facebook is the second person
will be no yes why are they checking you
checking you they are checking you are a good
student or not without you
therefore this week and Burova computer
will be like your husband and she screams he wants to make
sure they have learned he wants to
remind you don't think that Buddha is not
very good you will learn
more from problems than from no problems
[music]
the person who creates problems for you
you have a lot of mothers new house 7
when we don't have problems we don't remember by
articles when we have a problem we
remember about the emptiness furniture from the bureau
now maybe this person who
creates a problem for you he is a year and maybe
not low tides donu in fact we
don't know like the Bible maybe I will be alone
maybe I won't fall more as if I
think
but for us it is more useful if we think
that he is like therefore be there will be a husband
who yells at you he is like she
decided I don't know if it is possible
yes maybe this bureau if they will
conclusions I hope your kanti gamal kunki
screamed bunny  You in such a way that
you think about emptiness, perhaps you are
quite wild on this, it's logical and drone
Hardee's and
you don't need to talk and shale we
will my husband will definitely be Agisheva
told me this is true and Navalny on
our level
in the end, can we honestly say
maybe they if Buddha you don't
respect him then I'll tell you a story I
was in the diamond business 19 and at the beginning of my
life the company could not pay me a
salary I worked backen DPD we
had no money at all we couldn't
pay salaries even during breaks
and then we
asked if we could pay salaries
the next week we were told the debt
maybe you were gone for a day you can go out
cheated
sometimes 6 pay then we became the
largest diamond company for diamond
jewelry at home but have of memory
I gave half of my money directly
without tax and they gave half they
climbed okay internet and Gotham and Bass
and I had to go for six months and on
ions you owe me what 200 thousand
dollars and today I give this
monastery  and he talks about how much from
200,000 to him to reach McQueen
and let's do 300,000
and he gave another 100,000 the
branch is cool it's on
fire this is for your monster
and we've been doing this for many years understand Honda in the
end he gave me a very large
amount on top can I ask you a personal
question what is he talking about before the stable spam
flaw
he Israel I hope they are all Jews rule
you from Israel before but all the people took they are
such tough Jews why are you giving
extra money in a Buddhist
monastery
every time you give an extra ton of money
my duda
why are you doing this young but we are
icy you soon
never know which religion is
correct
ok
especially possible where is sister
Judaism from here is correct maybe
Christianity maybe Islam is correct w
- that is click
maybe your monastery one percent
therefore a smart person gives everyone don't top up
Avtodor and when
therefore after Michael's death good
instead of going these are the
people who yell at you people
who create problems for you we don't know
who will be better respect each person
perhaps this Buddha  Perhaps
we don't know this and its benefits are different religions,
perhaps some are wrong, but this is not a
problem that I will not, this is also you
still create a good seed, so it is
more let's be safer wherever I
wish, excellent for food, and pick up as I
am the seas of cheap, they said that when
he goes to a cafe, all will come to
look at us
because we create things from the outside, well,
I want to know, Buddha, after all, from which
side does it exist, from his side is the
second head with legs, and this head is
called coming and going in the bureau,
computer, world, if I were to come from
me, why should I even ask him to
come to Inna Burik when it seems that he
comes to an IT company, he comes from you, there are
two in the hotel with the stone of arrival, the first
Buddha comes to this company, but he
comes, comes from you,
and where is he, their request,
I will give you an example, salt or review, I live
in a small town,
remarks to impose a small town in
China, inspection, New
York is a small town, it's
true, but my city is super small,
vital, I think 3,000 people with us and
we have a post office,
periscope  And there for women and work I will
find you I think they are already 90 years old you
write a letter give him a call you
need allows and not give I think they are
sleeping there they do they take the letter and they
send it it expert in after post
I have 15 minutes to walk to the post office
Ippo and boiled if I write a letter where is
this Michael boundary and Michael
and find from here he or I take it to the
elderly woman's address and myself two
weeks
to get to Persian faces
hearts and the rest
well let's say I wrote a letter I'm Michael
and to give it stupid and phantom you
really are stupid you fool I folded it like this packed
gave it to the elderly
woman and two weeks later he became an
interrogation not lyubly the postman and is waiting for the side
I think he is the son of the elderly woman video
and he will give you milk I will open it it says
I hung a fool to me
Steve question you should I be
angry at the postman who brought
me the letter well no and we take writers
he  He didn't write, he just delivered. Your husband
is the postman. You wrote the letter. He
just put it to you. When your husband is at
war, and Stan, whether you have nuances,
he delivers your seeds and Tencrisa.
If your husband criticizes you, who
wrote the letter?
Don't kill Pascal. Young Bin will blow. He didn't
do anything. He just delivered
your own letter. Write when your
husband criticizes you. He's just
the postman. He didn't write the letter. You wrote it. Do
you understand now why I hung it up? He
talks about it himself, like asthma.
Some people ask me how to
remember.
For example, when I take spirin
and I have a problem. I take aspirin. Does it
work or not?
Santos. Sometimes, if you helped people with
headaches in the past,
if you planted a seed so that the
medicine would work, then the medicine will
work for you. And if you ignored
your friend who had a headache
when Rime died, everyone's body is on, but
it won't work.
Yoga is
for the same reason. Some people go to
yoga classes and become strong.
Anatolyevna
Samba.  pa ti samples some people
go to the same classes but feel uneasy time for
15 late
classes this is the postman aspirin this is the
postman they didn't write a letter you see she has
when you starbucks and train
your friend's pens endo bureau scan tool and buddha
comes to you and will come to you they come to me do they come
to you as if do
n't forget three questions the first duet
if I have a pen in my hand
secret to be company if I have a pen in my hand
which comes from me
if I have a pen in my hand which
comes from the pen wouldn't new tests
when you train pens at starbucks should it come like
cancer will it come as if before the casino there was
question number two gold century depends whether
they come thanks to your seeds on
was or burak will any buddha come
to starbucks
while you train pens
which does not come from you no but did
buddha come so don't forget
question 3 always ask yourself then you
won't get confused
if the pen is in my hand yes if the pen is in
my hand which comes from me before
if the pen which comes from the pen
no if the buddha who came to the cafe  without
yours,
not from your senate, that's what the
volunteers studied at the top, our subject was 8
impossibility means it can't
happen, not in the know, happened from yours,
sinan, no, they don't come from yours,
we
[music]
Yasha, are you
waiting, I have it
myself, I'm Jan Sandal, Belinda
already googled who for the sake of help, the most penda zone,
I'm smart, Putin's drunk and the sheriff's wife's zhime, I
clarified the maps, just a question, since
our seeds set our world, we can
see the world created by our seeds. If
I want to be an example for other people,
then how can I influence other
people? I'm confused with the county cache. I didn't
wake up the Boeing. I was born a
Christian and my mother has four of us,
and my mother took us to church,
they didn't like him, because it was very
cool.
I still go to the same church
where we went, the children will be. I know the smell,
I like the feeling
and prayer, very similar to the mide, then past
was moving, and my mother took us to
church and said, malice, but so did the
paths of the snake, many of
his, Castel hair, will come into the hands of
Christianity and  you understand mom
says fold your hands like this we'll extract it
just like that hands
she says put it down wife close your eyes
we close your eyes think about all the
people in the world
think about the whole world movies were at home and
these funny they believe mom
they are like that mine love everyone in everyone it's difficult these
elections
she says pray for everyone then what to
help we try the center when we are from
Korea and children believe everything they are
lucky you are not girl dress up
when will you stop older same
problem shear talking muggles if I
can't help everyone the whole world is
bombing and evil by the way I have oc we will still need
if you have announcing with
me
I will give you a couple of minutes for and well and you with Shane
I was trained
besides my mom to
think about the whole world of a person and try to
help them
legalized for everything for metal for about 20 years
as I said I say mom but they do this for
small children it's normal for him
but when mom grows up it's already
impossible to change the whole world one
person can't change the whole world
yubico son and you become cynical with me
but such it's
impossible golden so I would
say fusing a couple of years  back and
teacher well you I taught Norwegians love
smoking last year there was a scream decided
lucky he looks just like Thor I
hate this guy
emergency Hanson incredibly cute long
blond long hair
muscles his need we new his family is also
one of the richest families
brought here yours see three there is a reason
why I hate him water and the first is
hair he has hair on 2 strong
thread
incredibly rich set the worst is
number four
he is incredibly kind and it is very difficult
to envy him
or
in general I went to his country I
taught us time seeds billing and
the name
one many person classes on him and
says you know from the form x gods I always
wanted what was stupidity for girls I want
someone to me the words Kinderkraft
so I came to your class but
now I understand the industry what to do
what to do
she saved there are famous restaurants lepi
weather
here many people go today Alla year
succeeded
I will go to this restaurant Alu Plus and you are
smart for I will kiss every woman in this
restaurant Almaty full I am  Tag sessions
and find a girl who will wait for me.
Women are also available. If you want a
partner, Unity Player. You need to
sow the seed of diodes. If you want to sow the
seed, they can do it.  But he and you need to find a
lonely person, Defense Jersey and Yaga,
equal once and offered from above and
another offer in her:
go to a nursing home and radio an elderly
woman once a week, water and in the cinema, the
office of the moon, she's lonely, that there is no family
that I visit, payment of amounts, and you
fast
when you meet your girlfriend, soldiers,
Akim, I return home on the air somewhere
six weeks after this year and
worlds and I receive from him, Mel,
I went, it worked, I went to
let down my grandmother, the Okinawans sowed the seed and on the
players and I got a girlfriend, an
excellent game system, move away to and now
sex, we are in the world in another 6 months,
agate stock, I get 2 mail.ru
and in it a video
moving towards there, like Harry and Ron, world,
details of this
will get to the Tyumen woman, this video is the answer
two minutes before underwear and my faithful son, a
mouse, a video in Norwegian,
I don't know what they say, and Sochi nights,
but they always say officials, then
The same as the movie
means the same thing, ...
and Luke Levicheva decided to give his
Rebecca a sweet
comfort and a lot of salad, and they were still being conducted for the
village, to the will of the
godfather's chances, he now himself fears
succeeded in the dark
[music]
and
[applause]
discs replay this video in Norway
they play every week shared for
the video funcom were
this video paid for by the national local
telephone company new and the
government of Norway and tzu at the end it
says that
if a young man takes an elderly
person to the cinema and the ball is over his head a rake
and the national telephone company,
together with the government, will pay for both
tickets, you need to put or and about the next
gibt es wird how this video began
now or in the compartment hundreds of thousands of people
are taken away hundreds of thousands of young people
are allocated detach grandmothers and knew every
week and how it all started with
you you became Dmitry Galkin dream guy
who decided not to kiss all the
girls in the restaurant
started with him 1 person got his
girlfriend friends then asked how you have
n't had a girlfriend for five years somehow at all and
where are you  He found her, meaning that you did it seemingly
brazenly. Go, you need to sow the seed. He
plotted the elderly of his friends and hands,
put them under the gods, then each other
received each other, each other also
received a girl, fostex, double vision,
virus 4, upset in Narva, key from
one song from one person destroys
all the people in. So there are two
ways to help all people. You love
the mind, you can sit in church with your mother. I would
like to help everyone. Let you blow,
so you can. These years are a good thing, and before
zombies, a gift. Whether it doesn't help people
directly,
but indirectly, is a good way,
or
you do now, use these four steps.
You yourself will become a memory of defects and
become financially successful. You will be
complete and become healthy, and in the south, to the
top, thousands,
create, you will create about different attitudes, a
happy marriage,
underwear, then your friends will start to make you a hero of
their own,
and friends of friends will be, and their friends will be, under the
copier.  But my makeup, soap, and dietary supplements,
and the substances will create a movie, you will be a
star there, you understand, court fingers Uganda is the
best thing you can do.
Help everyone, to help everyone, use God, it's
impossible for a user to take
four steps. Become successful yourself,
and people will simply start copying you.
So, really, you can
help the whole world. Analysis:
Every person has the power to aria, resentment,
what to do. You will succeed. You should be
happy. Marriage, be loved, be
healthy, be happy. This is
human advertising. Understand, thank you.
[Applause]